this problem requires us to
use a for loop to iterate over the
friends
in our friend's array and greet each one
of them individually
and we've been given some expected
output so that we know how to
format our greeting but first let's just
get started on our for loop
remember that in a for loop we use a
named variable to
represent each element of the collection
that we're iterating through
[Music]
if we call our variable friend it's
pretty clear that
we're referring to one individual out of
our array of friends
[Music]
and we can just start out here by
outputting
friends
and you can see that we successfully
output each element of the friends array
now we could use any variable name that
we want here
there's nothing that dictates that we
need to call it
friend however let's say we use
the variable n our code still runs
just exactly the same however n is not a
clear or descriptive variable name for
these elements
now let's consider how we can output a
greeting that
matches the expected output we were
given
we need to output a string
[Music]
that says hello and greets the friend by
name
followed by an exclamation point
there are two different ways that we can
achieve this output
and the first way that we'll look at is
concatenation
[Music]
so we can use concatenation to simply
insert the element
into our string output
in running our code you can see that our
output matches the expected output
now let's consider another way that we
can achieve the expected output
and that's through string interpolation
string interpolation has a special
syntax
using the pound signed and curly braces
and we can
insert our variable name in here
and we'll see the same output